the cops determine our attitude towards them
менты определяют наше отношение к ним
or our attitude towards garbage determines
или наше отношение к мусорам определяет
the garbage Hello, I’m from the city of
мусоров Здравствуйте я из города
Khmelnitsk
Хмельницке Вы
Where are you from Chelyabinsk, cool I’ll be
откуда из Челябинска прикольно Я вот
honest, this is the first time I’ve seen such an
честно говоря первый раз так вижу такое
association of Adidas and for it They
объединение Adidas и на него Вот это
found an emblem there, it’s cool I
нашли эмблему там прикольно
understand yes
понимаю
Well, you said correctly they’re tuning  there And
Ну вы правильно сказали тюнингуют там А
that there are all sorts of collaborations
что всякие коллаборации там есть
there, don’t you think you think it’s
там не вы считаете вы считаете это
somehow shameful or something, it’s not
как-то зазорно что ли или что нене не
just that this is the first time I’ve seen something like that, well, we have it
просто я впервые вижу такое что вот ну у
there, for example, if Adidas buys Well,
нас там например если покупает Adidas Ну
nothing is ours, but they found something like, well,
ничего не нашева ну а так нашли типа ну
this  interesting Well, yes, you see, as long as we have the
это интересно А ну да у нас видите лишь
money to do everything And so it wasn’t
бы бабки чтобы делались всё А так это не
you who found it, you actually bought it Well, of
вы сами нашли это Вы прям купили такое
course, you mean
Ну естественно вы
this is
что вот
Factory All I think it’s a
это Фабричная Всё я думаю это так
badge I understand I don’t care about this It’s
нашивка понял Ни фига себе при это Это
not me who bought it Well,  you bought a
не я купил Ну а вы купили с этой
ready-made one with this stripe, yes Yes, a long time ago
нашивкой уже готовую да Да давно ещё
Damn, to be honest, I probably understood it back
Блин если честно назад ещ наверно понял
And they didn’t sell it without stripes.
А без нашивок не продавали
To be honest, I don’t know, I understand what you’re talking about here,
о Если честно не знаю понял о чём тут
just about human things about human things about
просто о человеческом о людском о
human things, about human things. Who do you
людском да о людском Да с кем как
think the cops are messing around with?  in
считаешь менты беспредельничает в
Russia there are cops
России менты
Yes
Да
there are And in Ukraine they are not
есть А в Украине что они не
lawless we them we them on mine
беспредельничает мы их мы их на мой
We after the Maidan In short we started them and
Мы после Майдана Короче мы зач их и всё
they are all now obedient normal none of them
они теперь послушные нормальные никто их
just how many bloggers have watched
просто сколько много блогеров смотрел
your Ukrainian Well how
ваших украинских Ну как
Well these traffic police officers how they
Ну этих дпсников как они
tamed after the Maidan  there is no traffic police officer
приручали после Майдана уже нет ДПСника
anymore, well, well, maybe I haven’t
всё уже ну не ну может быть может быть я
known for a year, uh, like they came out in short.
ни году знаешь ээ типа вышли короче Вот
It was Berkut and Yanukovych and the people came out
был это Беркут и Янукович и народ вышел
with slogans against garbage thieves, like this, it
с лозунгами против воров мусоров вот так
turns out that the thieves ran away to Rostov and
типа получается воры убежали в Ростов и
who went where? Yes, but the garbage guys in short were disbanded
кто куда Да а мусоров короче распустили
and they took the normal police, they recruited like
и взяли нормальную полицию набрали типа
Berkut, they disbanded it so that he would
Беркут распустили это да чтобы он людей
n’t beat people Yes, and they did everything clearly It’s all
не бил Да и сделали Всё чётко Всё
real, now you’re coming Yes,
реально вот сейчас приходишь Да
the policeman communicates with you normally, he doesn’t
полицейский к тебе общается нормально не
say I’d charge you now with a scoreboard Yes there is That’s it, that’s
говорит я тебя сейчас б в табло заряжу
all there is And
Да есть Вот вот вот и всё и есть И это
you understand this correctly because
правильно понимаешь потому что
a policeman, too, is a human being with people,
полицейский тоже человеки с людьми
must speak like a human being, and so we
должен по-людски говорить так и мы
did. Like in Europe, the policeman
сделали Как в Европе та что полицейский
speaks like a human being
человеком говорит по-людски
to a human being, and what is human is human, you understand this is
а людское - это людское понимаешь это
humanism Yes, humanism Yes, but here,
гуманизм Да гуманизм Да а у нас
as you yourself know, Well, here you go
как сами знаете Ну
Do you remember how, in the era of
вот вот помниш как е вот в эпоху
Enlightenment, yes, he wrote that let’s say the
Просвещения да писал что скажем э
police shouldn’t do that
полиция так не должна
- the police should beat, the police should
- бить полиция должна
serve, serve Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, they
служить служить Да да да вот да да она
should show the face of power. Well, yes, yes,
должна показывать лицо власти Ну да да
then in letters to Descartes, like yes, he
вот он тогда в письмах декарту типа да
expressed his thoughts about this,
высказывал свои мысли об этом
yes
да
I understand So just like that yes Well, it doesn’t matter
понял Так что вот так вот да
how they were in Sarani they are
Ну всё равно как му Сарани были они так
and are everywhere that we have that somewhere else I
и есть везде что у нас что где-то ещё
don’t know them yet until they themselves die out
пока их не знаю пока они сами не вымрут
or what I don’t
или что я вот не
know How would I just like that I even
знаю Как бы мне вот просто я даже про
I don’t want to say anything about them no no Well,
них не хочу ничего говорить не не Ну
look from the point of view of the philosophical
смотри вот с точки зору философского
context, so there is here being
контекста так вот есть вот там бытиё
determines consciousness or consciousness
определяет сознание либо сознание
determines being and so the question is whether the
определяет бытиё так вот вопрос это
cops determine our attitude towards them
менты определяют наше отношение к ним
or our attitude towards garbage determines
или наше отношение к мусорам определяет
garbage This is the
мусоров Вот это такой
question that can  look, uh, when we
вопрос может смотрите э когда мы на них
let them yell at them, well, what the hell are you
допустим кричим Да ну то что вы какие-то
doing, they’re looking at us, it’s because you
хе они на нас смотрят то что вот вы нас
don’t
не
understand us, this is our job. And when, from
понимаете это наша работа А когда с
our point of view, we say this,
нашей точки зрения мы это утверждаем
like, what the hell are you guys, we’re the
типа мужики вы какого хрена Мы же ну
people, yeah  we are all united Why the hell are you
народ Да мы все единые Какого хрена вы
going against us They look differently
против нас идёте Они по-другому смотрят
and tell us Well, this is our job Damn,
и говорят нам Ну это же наша работа Блин
why the hell is this our job You,
ну какого хрена это наша работа Ты же
let’s say, you’re my grandfather, you’re my father Yes, you’re
допустим ты мой дед ты мой отец Да
standing Now against me, yes Well, it
стоишь Сейчас против меня вот да Ну
turns out, yes, look We  we think badly about the
получается да смотри Мы плохо думаем о
Muras because they are bad or they are
мурах потому что они плохие или они
bad because we think badly about them, that’s
плохие из-за того что мы о них плохо
what comes
думаем вот что
first, look, our power is to push them
первично смотрите их власть наша задрать
to such an extent that they tell us
до такой степени чтобы они нам говорили
these words That’s all, that’s all More nothing
вот такие слова Вот и
more yes
всё вот и всё Больше Больше никак да
they  - they will tell us any words because
они-то скажут нам любые слова потому что
they get money for it, they
они за это получают деньги они на эти
feed their family with this money, but I
деньги кормят свою семью а больше
don’t understand anything else to my wife, by the way, hello wife, I
никак понял жене кстати привет жена я
hear Yes, yes, look, Yes, it
слышу Да гово Да так вот смотри Да тут
turns out that I am still a
получается что я вс-таки
supporter of the fact that, uh, we are forming  that is, it is
сторонник того что ээ мы формируем вот
not the police who shape us, but we who
то есть не полиция формирует нас а мы
shape the police, yes, that is, uh, we are not a
формируем полицию да то есть ээ не мы
reflection of the state and the police, but the
есть отображение государства и полиции а
police are a reflection of us, if we
полиция есть отображение нас если мы
think it’s the norm to beat a person, and
считаем Это нормой побить человека Да и
the police consider it the norm, yes, we
полиция считает это нормой Да мы
project on the police, and our
проектируем на полицию Да свои
philosophical views on  life yes And
философские воззрения на жизнь да И вот
if you
если
look from the point of view uh here's how he wrote
смотреть с точки зрения ээ вот как писал
niche so this is all he wrote uh the
нише так вот это всё он писал э
famous book Yes that's what
известную книгу Да так говорил
Zarathustra said and he described the moment when
заратустра и он описывал момент когда
a policeman detained a guy like this at the police station in
задерживают полицейский Да в отделении в
Paris The guy was black
Париже парня так Парень чернокожий был
Yes they beat him
Да они его избивают
and people  people stand up, they stand up for an unfamiliar
и люди встают люди встают за незнакомого
guy, so that’s what the niche called it,
парня так вот и ниша это назвал
that unity is in separation Yes, that
что единение в разъединении Да что
everyone is scattered I don’t know him He does
каждый разрозненный Я не знаю его Он не
n’t know me, no one else knows, but everyone
знает меня никто другой не знает но все
stands up together against the tyranny of
вместе встают против проти произвола
Mussorsky Yes, because this is mass,
Мусорского Да потому что это есть обедня
you go and see garbage  someone is beating yes You are for
ты идёшь видишь мусор кого-то бьёт да Ты
whom you will be You don’t know
за кого будешь Вот ты не знаешь из-за
why you think you are trash or because of who they are
чего ты думаешь за мусора или изза того
beating who they are beating because I don’t know, yes yes And
бьют кого бьют потому что зна не охуеваю
that’s what I’m saying inishe yes
да да И это вот и говорю инише да назвал
he called it he called it
это он назвал
and not
этои не
above
выде
I  I think I’ll
Я дума я
sign up for th Telegram right now axis VN
запишись на й Telegram прям зараз ось ВН
apok tse more and more respectfully YouTube is busy with
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through SR grv your ban and a lot more
нас через СР грв твый бан и дуже багато
videos don’t show people immediately don’t show
вдео не показуе людям вчасно не показуе
information about streams so that
информация про стримы тому для того щоб
we Mali operational link to write
мы Мали оперативный звязок пишиться
directly for apok  there in telegra okrim video
прямо за а пок там в телегра окрим видео
sche tezh tsikava and korisna information and mi
ще теж цикава и корисна информация и ми
vinni z you trimati postiyny
повинни з вами тримати постийний
operational link
оперативный звязок
nezalezhno in that chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава Украине
letter
пись